<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
	xmlns:sparkle="http://sparkle.andymatuschak.org/rss/1.0/modules/sparkle/">
  <channel>
    <title>Stacksmith nightly Appcast</title>
    <link>http://stacksmith.org/</link>
    <description>Updates for Stacksmith</description>
    <item>
       <title>Stacksmith 1.0a11 (1765)</title>
       <link>https://github.com/uliwitness/Stacksmith/releases/download/Stacksmith_1_0_a11_1765/Stacksmith.tgz</link>
       <description>&lt;h3&gt;2019-02-21&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scripts now copy RSS into source tree where it needs to be for Github Pages,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nicer formatting of commit message list in release notes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Now have one &quot;build-and-upload&quot; script.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Release script now actually works!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We were parsing the JSON wrong and thus truncating the upload URL.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For now, make our releases drafts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WIP on a script that uploads a release to Github that was built using the nightly_build.command script&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It successfully creates the release, but the upload fails (but can be done via the website).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2019-02-20&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prettify the code snippet list a bit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add icons to a few of the message snippets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2019-02-19&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make dropping snippets in a script work properly: You can't drop inside a handler, only between them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WIP on making snippet insertion work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oops wromg suffix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Icon picker cleanup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2019-02-18&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Icon picker now correctly shows the selection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Icon picker now displays images again, though hit-testing still seems to be intercepted by the icon and label.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Touch-ups to magnifying glass.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Better object (&quot;file&quot;) names in debugger.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;2019-02-17&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the magnifying glass, add message watcher, variable watcher and message box icons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make non-native tool palette not clip.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update Copyright year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track Forge HEAD for #54 bugfix in Leonie.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another round of icon updates so Mike won't be too sad about what I've done to his great icon design in the process of making a vector version :-S&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use the new icon re-draw for the app icon itself and make them easier to re-generate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I'm not sure why the doc icon won't be generated by Xcode from the asset catalog, so I renamed the .appicon to .iconset, re-assigned the sizes, and when that didn't help used iconutil --convert icns on it to generate an old-fashioned WILDDocIcon.icns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add text edit tool to palette.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move the front/back scripts from a global into the context group where they belong.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Funnily, I had started putting them there ages ago, it seems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We now insert the tools card as a frontscript to update its buttons when the tool changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WIP on adding &quot;insert script&quot; command so we have front scripts our tool palette can use to hear of tool changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
       <enclosure url="https://github.com/uliwitness/Stacksmith/releases/download/Stacksmith_1_0_a11_1765/Stacksmith.tgz" length="9865665" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:dsaSignature="MC4CFQCjj/TPKsKcCWhDjVM0uk/NUQYUngIVAIwb3GLxPlIZyBSIQ/aZrPOcT4eY" />
       <sparkle:version>1.0a11 (1765)</sparkle:version>
     </item>
  </channel>
</rss>